exponential.com 2013-12-23

# Privacy « Exponential InteractiveExponential Interactive

_Updated on September 6, 2012_

Exponential Interactive, Inc. (“Exponential”) is a technology-enabled media services company whose clients and customers include both online advertisers (“Advertisers”) and digital content providers (“Digital Content Providers”). We deliver innovative products and services designed to:

  * enable Advertisers to better reach their target audiences; and
  * enable Digital Content Providers to support, grow and monetize their properties through the sale of advertisements.

Our product offerings and services currently include Adotube, AppSnack, Firefly Video, FullTango, TechBargains and Tribal Fusion (together, referred to herein as our “Services”). For a full description of these Services please see our website at [www.exponential.com](http://www.exponential.com/).

At Exponential we believe that safe, secure and respectful practices regarding the use of consumer information are fundamental to our business success and to the growth and vitality of the Internet as a whole. We are a member of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”). We are signatories to the DAA AdChoices program and the EASA’s Best Practice Recommendation on Online Behavioral Advertising. We maintain compliance with the [NAI’s Self-Regulatory Principles](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/principles.asp) and [IAB UK’s Good Practice Principles](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/goodpractice.html).

This Privacy Policy is intended to provide consumers with clear and complete information about the consumer data we collect in connection with our Services and the way that data is stored and used by our company, our clients and partners. For information about our privacy practices as they relate to our corporate website, please see below.

#### Information We Collect

**Non-Personal Information Collected by our Services**  
We deliver advertisements from hundreds of Advertisers across a multitude of Digital Content Provider properties. When you visit one of these properties, our automated system may collect “click stream data” related to your visit to the property. Click stream data is anonymous and can include information such as your IP address, content or pages viewed, the date and time at which that content was viewed and any interaction with content and advertisements on those properties. Technologies used to collect this click stream data include cookies and Web beacons.

In order to improve performance, we augment our click stream data with non-personally-identifiable behavioral and demographic data from Digital Content Providers and other partners. This anonymous data may include such things as postal code, age and gender. It may also include GPS location provided by Digital Content Providers with mobile properties.

**Personally Identifiable Information Collected By Our Tech Bargains Service**  
Tech Bargains is a consumer-facing site where you may sign up to get alerts on discount deals. In registering for the service, you may choose to provide personally identifiable information such as your name and/or email address. Exponential will not merge any of this Tech Bargains personally identifiable information with any non-personally identifiable information collected by our systems (including systems for all other Exponential divisions) and will not use this personally identifiable information in any way that is not authorized by the user from whom it is collected. In addition, we keep this data in a separate database to ensure that advertisements are delivered only through the utilization of anonymous consumer data.

**Personally Identifiable Information Collected Through Our Corporate Website**  
You may also provide us with personally identifiable information (such as your name, email address, physical address or telephone number) when you elect to contact us about this Privacy Policy or any other customer-service related matter. We will only utilize such personal information for the purpose of responding to your inquiry. However, we do reserve the right to retain an archival record of all such correspondence.

We reserve the right to disclose personally identifiable information you have disclosed to us in response to judicial process or court order or to provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation of matters related to public safety, as permitted by law.

#### How We Use Collected Data

We utilize the non-personal information described above to better customize the sort of advertisements you see. We also aggregate anonymous cookie data in order to identify large audience segments that assist advertisers in targeting their campaigns to the most relevant Internet audience.

We may use click stream data as well as cookie data for non-targeting reasons such as frequency capping, compliance, fraud prevention, billing, service fulfilment, ad reporting or delivery, market research or product development within the permissions of the NAI/DAA Principles and EDAA Framework.

Our anonymous tracking cookies are programmed to expire in ninety days from the last time we encounter you, at which point the web browser will delete them automatically.

We store non-personally identifiable information in log files, which may be retained in our systems indefinitely. Anonymous data stored in our log files that associates the log data to a particular browser or device include IP address and User ID. We purge the IP address and irreversibly obfuscate the User ID from our log files six months after collection of this information.

This information may also be combined with data from other sources, and shared with our affiliates and partners for similar use.

#### Consumer Choice – Opting Out of Behavioral Advertising

We use technology which includes cookies and web beacons in the delivery of our Services. We believe that the use of these tools enables us to provide users with a more meaningful web experience.

We enable consumer choice and control over our third party tracking cookie. The details of this cookie can be found below. For details of our other cookies, please contact [privacy@exponential.com](mailto:privacy@exponential.com).

You may opt out of being behaviorally targeted by Exponential online advertising via [our opt-out mechanism](http://exponential.com/success/).

Through this opt-out procedure, your computer will overwrite our ANON_ID cookie with a non-identifying “opt-out” cookie that indicates your anonymous data should not be used for behaviorally targeted advertising. Please note that the “opt-out” cookie must remain on your computer in order for us to recognize you as an opt-out user. This means that if you use multiple computers or multiple browsers you will need to opt out of receiving cookies on each computer and for each browser. Also, if you change computers or delete cookies from your computer you will need to repeat this opt-out process. The details of the opt-out cookie are shown below.

You can also opt out of being behaviorally targeted by Exponential and other companies employing online advertising via the [NAI’s opt-out mechanism ](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)or IAB Europe’s [youronlinechoices](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/) site.

You may also adjust your computer’s web browser settings to refuse all cookies. However, please note that because cookies are widely used, disabling the use of cookies in your web browser may interfere with full use of various websites.

Personally identifiable information collected by Exponential on its own behalf may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Exponential or its affiliates, subsidiaries, agents or customers maintain facilities. You acknowledge and agree that personally identifiable information you provide to us may be transferred outside of the country in which you reside. Providing such information will constitute your consent to any such transfer.

#### Information Security

Exponential follows generally accepted industry standards to protect against unauthorized access to, destruction or disclosure of data. This includes undertaking physical, electronic and management activities to protect data integrity, access and use. Any data that is stored on our servers is treated as confidential and is not made generally available to the public. Our servers are protected by firewalls and are located in secure data facilities to further increase security. Please keep in mind, however, that despite these reasonable efforts to protect data on our servers no method of transmission over the Internet is guaranteed to be secure. Therefore, while we strive to protect your personal data at all times, we cannot guarantee its absolute security and shall not be liable for any breach of security by an outside party.

#### Transfer of Data Upon Change of Control

In the event that another company acquires all or substantially all of the assets of our business through a consolidation, merger, asset purchase or other transaction, we reserve the right to transfer all data (including any personally identifiable data) that is in our possession or under our control to such acquiring party.

#### Children’s Privacy

Exponential is sensitive to the issue of children’s privacy. Hence, our services are neither developed for, nor directed at, children. We don’t offer the targeting of advertising towards anyone under the age of 13.

#### Healthcare Privacy

Exponential allows advertisers to target users in certain health-related categories. A list of these categories may be found [here](http://exponential.com/healthcare-privacy-policy/).

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy by posting an updated version on this page. The date on which the current Privacy Policy was posted will always be noted at the top of this page. Any change we make to our Privacy Policy will be made in compliance with applicable law.

#### Correspondence

If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence, including your email address. This relates to your correspondence with us only – we do not gather users’ email addresses as part of our online advertising business.

We are committed to following the [IAB UK Good Practice Principles](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/goodpractice.html). If you feel we are breaching those Principles, you should contact us at [privacy@exponential.com](mailto:privacy@exponential.com). If contacting us does not resolve the complaint, you should follow the IAB UK complaint procedures at [www.youronlinechoices.co.uk/how-do-i-make-a-complaint](http://www.youronlinechoices.co.uk/how-do-i-make-a-complaint).

#### Questions and Comments

Questions and comments regarding this Privacy Policy should be directed to [privacy@exponential.com](mailto:privacy@exponential.com)or mailed to:

Exponential Interactive, Inc., 2200 Powell Street, Suite 600, Emeryville, CA 94608, Attn: Legal Department.

Copyright © 2012 Exponential Interactive Inc. All Rights Reserved.
